[theme music playing]
[frightening music plays]
[reporter on radio] Dear citizens,
this is an announcement
from the emergency broadcast system.
Due to this unforeseen
and rapidly escalating situation,
the government is taking
all possible precautionary measures
- to ensure public safety.
- [groans]
Emergency services
on Suseo-bound line three trains
will resume at 1800 hours today.
Trains will begin service...
- [grunts]
- ...at Daehwa Station
and will stop at Jongno three-ga Station,
Express Bus Terminal Station,
and Dogok Station.
[inhales, grunts]
All other stops are suspended.
SITE MANAGER: WE HAVE A MAJOR PROBLEM
SECURITY: PLEASE PICK UP
SITE MANAGER: CALL ME
MOM: ARE YOU OKAY?
Trains will begin service
at Daehwa Station
and will stop at Jongno...
[retches, coughs]
...Express Bus Terminal Station,
and Dogok Station.
- [grunts]
- Local authorities recommend
evacuating the city center at once.
Again, all other stops...
- Shit. I need to clean this.
- ...all routes have been suspended.
Avoid crowded areas and make your way to
the nearest emergency service station.
If you're sheltering in place
and unable to safely evacuate,
please reach out to emergency services
for additional assistance.
[sighs] So fucked up.
[grunting]
[drumroll beating]
[heroic music playing]
[gulping]
Mmm.
[zombies snarling]
[retches]
[zombies hissing]
[grunts]
Jesus Christ. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
[pensive music playing]
JEON HYUNG-BAE
PARK SUNG-WOOK
- Sergeant Kim Young-man?
- [Young-man] Huh?
Huh?
You gotta stay strong for us.
Now that First Sergeant is gone,
we need you to lead us.
That's right.
I guess... I have the highest rank here.
- Soo-jeong.
- Yes.
We need to get out as quickly as we can.
How can we get to the lower levels?
The VIP lounge
has an elevator we can access.
- That'd be the quickest.
- Okay.
[Jae-yoon] And, sir...
I believe...
these belong to you as our new leader.
[Young-man breathing shakily]
[sniffles]
- It's as heavy as I thought it'd be.
- [Jae-yoon sobs]
[Gye-young sobbing]
- [Young-man] Let's get ready.
- [all] Let's get ready!
- [Soo-jeong sniffles]
- [Paolo] Gye-young...
I'm scared, dude.
[Young-man] Packed your gear?
[Kyung-sik] Everything's packed.
- [Young-man] Pack anything that--
- Grab a gun if you wanna live, Paolo.
You're gonna have to learn
to take care of yourself now.
- [Young-man] Help me.
- [Paolo sighs]
[Kyung-sik] All right, I got it.
Shit. They warned me
of the Three Calamities.
SAMJAE:
THE 3 CALAMITIES HUMANS FACE EVERY 9 YEARS
[heroic music playing]
[drill whirring]
[whirring continues]
[staple gun clicks]
[scoffs]
[zombies snarling]
[heroic music playing]
Ladies and gentlemen!
[snarling]
Please, do not walk around
on your bloody feet.
This is a luxury hotel.
[Arron Park] Yes!
This is a five star service, you bastards!
[Arron Park] Bullseye.
[snarling continues]
Yes!
[laughing]
[reporter on radio] Emergency services
on Suseo-bound line three trains
will resume at 1800 hours today.
Please note that trains
will begin service at Daehwa Station,
and will stop at Jongno three-ga Station,
Express Bus Terminal Station,
and Dogok Station.
All other stops have been suspended.
Once again, trains will begin service
at Daehwa Station,
and will stop at Jongno three-ga Station,
Express Bus Terminal Station,
and Dogok Station.
Local authorities recommend
evacuating the city center at once.
- [cars honking horn]
- All other stops along all routes
are suspended. If you are sheltering...
[Jin-wook sighs] Goddamn.
What's with the traffic.
Why are there so many cars?
[reporter on radio]
...additional assistance.
What's going on over there?
It's not moving at all.
What the hell is happening?
[gasps] Zombies can't get to us
if we're in here, right?
We're good. I don't see any zombies here.
[sighs] Thank God
- [men shouting indistinctly]
- Let's get outta here.
- [Jin-wook] You're right.
- [Young-joo gasps]
What? What? Wait!
- Bullshit.
- What?
[both yelling]
[man 1] Get 'em out.
- Get outta there.
- [Young-joo screams]
Young-joo! Young-joo!
Young-joo!
- [crying] What the fuck?
- You... You son of a bitch!
- [Young-joo screams]
- [Jin-wook grunts]
Get out, shithead.
- [Young-joo] What's wrong with you people?
- [man 1] Get out!
[man 2] Yeah.
[Young-joo cries]
- [Jin-wook] Whoa!
- [man 2] Get out!
- [man 2 grunts]
- [Jin-wook groaning]
[man 1] Come on! All right, let's go.
[man 3] Go around the right.
[cars honking horn]
[indistinct shouting]
Young-joo! You okay?
[people speaking indistinctly]
Everyone's gone crazy.
They've lost their damn minds.
Okay, hold on.
There's a terminal.
There's a terminal there.
[people clamoring indistinctly]
[Young-joo panting]
It's a shelter.
It's a shelter. [panting]
[sighs] Let's go.
- Yeah.
- [Young-joo mumbles]
It's packed.
[man on PA] Emergency trains are en route.
For your safety, please remain calm
and follow instructions.
The emergency trains will depart
from Daehwa Station...
[Jin-wook] Over there. Come on.
...at Jongno Three-ga,
Express Bus Terminal...
[Jin-wook] Excuse me.
The emergency trains
are now being deployed.
For your safety.
Please make sure to follow instructions.
- Line three, right?
- Yeah.
Let's take it to Suseo Station.
- Huh?
- It's the earliest train.
[sighs] Okay, okay. Let's keep going.
[man on PA] Once again,
the emergency trains are
now being deployed.
- [Young-man exhales]
- [elevator dings]
[Jae-yoon grunts]
- [Kyung-sik sighs]
- [In-ho] Careful.
[Soo-jeong] What the hell?
Why are you standing?
Get in here. Let's go.
[all panting]
[all breathing heavily]
- [elevator dings]
- [all exclaim]
[Soo-jeong gasps]
[all] Huh?
Hey, guys.
[both] Arron Park?
What's the hold up?
This line is going slower than usual.
- [kid grunts]
- [Young-joo] So sorry, kiddo.
Zombie girl.
- [all exclaiming]
- [kid] Zombie! Zombie!
- I'm not. I'm not.
- [man 1] She acting weird?
[Jin-wook] Go. Excuse me. Coming through.
[woman 1] She's acting weird.
- [woman 2] Don't push.
- Excuse us.
- [man 2] What's the hold up?
- [man on PA] ...train is now full
- [man 3] What's happening?
- [woman 3] We'll never leave!
[man 4] Come on. This is bullshit.
Cut... Cut that out. Stop pushing.
THIS TRAIN : SUSEO-BOUND
NEXT TRAIN: SUSEO-BOUND
[man 5] Come on, get to the front.
[man 6] What a disaster.
[woman 4] Why is nobody moving?
- [man 7] I was here first!
- [man on PA] Ladies and gentlemen...
- [Jin-wook] Keep up. Come here.
- [woman 5] Ah! That was my foot.
[man on PA] The emergency trains
are now being dispatched...
and we ask that you maintain
as much order as possible for your safety.
[man on PA] We also ask that passengers
who are unable to board the train...
remain calm and wait for the next train
inside the station.
[man on PA] We, the Seoul Metro,
are doing everything we can for you.
[man on PA] Thank you.
- [man 10] Where is it?
- Listen closely.
Board the train as quick as you can.
- All right.
- Stay next to me, okay?
- [man 11] That's my foot.
- I got it.
[man 12] Is it coming?
- [man 13] Hurry up.
- It's here.
[indistinct clamoring]
[woman on PA] Hello, and welcome.
The train bound
- for Suseo is now approaching.
- [man 14] See it!
Oh, go! Go, go, go.
[all clamoring]
Hey! Stop!
Young-joo, Young-joo. Young-joo.
- I can't. Oh, God.
- [Jin-wook] Young-joo.
Hold my hand. Just keep holding on, okay?
- [Young-joo] I'm slipping.
- [Jin-wook] Stop pushing.
[screaming]
Young-joo. Hold on. I've got you.
- [grunts]
- [Young-joo shouts]
- No!
- [Jin-wook] Young-joo.
[Young-joo screaming]
- [glass shattering]
- [train approaching]
[people screaming]
[clamoring continues]
[train whooshing]
[people screaming]
[cracking, squelching]
[brakes screeching]
[screaming continues]
Seo Jin-wook!
We need help here!
[all clamoring]
[both] Arron Park?
- [Soo-jeong] Manager?
- Ha! Soo-jeong.
Oh, it's the manager.
[grunts] In-ho, why did you do that?
Huh?
- [elevator door shutting]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [all gasping]
- [Paolo] What the hell?
- Your leg.
- Uh, he could have gotten that anywhere.
Uh, surely it isn't what we think.
It isn't right?
But it is. It was a zombie.
- You...
- Shit.
- [Arron Park] Whoa.
- What? What are you doing?
- Huh?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He told us he was bit, didn't he?
He could turn any minute.
He's a danger to us all.
He hasn't turned yet.
You need to relax and lower your gun.
That's right, soldier.
Kyung-sik, lower the gun, huh?
You asshole.
We need to keep moving
and get out of here.
Lower it.
Honestly, I don't think
he should ride with us either.
Let's close the door and keep going.
Wait, hold on for a second.
That bite was made
a couple of hours ago, right?
That means he isn't turning.
Since you aren't turning,
you can come with us.
No way in hell. It's too dangerous.
Let him come with us.
[Soo-jeong sobbing]
- Please, you guys.
- [Arron Park] It's okay.
He's right. It's too dangerous.
You guys go ahead.
[Soo-jeong sobbing]
Hey, look. [chuckles]
If I were to bite you...
[Soo-jeong crying]
I couldn't forgive myself for it.
Don't cry. Okay?
[heroic music playing]
Oh, wait. Wait.
Manager, uh, thank you for everything.
I will never forget you.
[sobbing]
- [loud thudding]
- [all exclaiming]
[Paolo] Oh, shit.
What is it?
[thudding continues]
[distant snarling]
- Get out now!
- [Soo-jeong yelps]
[zombies snarling]
- [indistinct yelling]
- [Young-joo crying]
[woman 1 crying]
You should get on. You can get on.
Come on.
[indistinct yelling continues]
[woman 2 sobbing]
[woman 3 on PA]
The train is about to depart.
Stay behind the yellow line
as the doors are closing.
- For your safety, please stand...
- Thank you.
- [kid] Grandma!
- [Grandma] Kyung-soo.
- [Kyung-soo] Grandma.
- [Grandma] It's okay.
It's okay. You'll be okay.
- [Kyung-soo] Grandma.
- Just get off at the last station.
- I'm so scared.
- [Grandma] Wait for me.
I'll be there soon.
- [Kyung-soo] Hurry.
- [Grandma] Kyung-soo.
- [Young-joo] It's leaving, careful.
- [Grandma] I'll get you. Wait.
- I'll find a way.
- [Kyung-soo crying]
Don't forget. Wait for me.
- [Young-joo] Please stop!
- No, no. I'll be there.
- Just wait!
- Please, come here.
[Grandma sobbing]
I promise he'll be okay.
[gasps]
[Grandma] Oh, God.
Kyung-soo!
[zombies snarling]
- [woman 4 screaming]
- [man yells] No!
[woman 5] No!
[pensive music playing]
[pensive music continues]
You saved me.
[Grandma breathing shakily]
I'll kill you.
[gasps] What are you doing?
- [Grandma panting]
- [cell phone ringing]
[woman 3] The train bound for Suseo...
- [Grandma] You fuckin' monsters.
- Wait.
- [Grandma] I'll kill you all.
- [Young-joo] Wait. Ma'am, wait.
- [Grandma] Kyung-soo!
- [indistinct announcement on PA]
Come back here, please.
It's too dangerous.
Ma'am. Wait.
[bell chiming]
- [Grandma] Kyung-soo!
- [train blowing horn]
[train continues blowing horn]
[brakes screeching]
[brakes thud]
- [gasps] Oh, my God.
- [woman 3] The doors are opening.
- [Young-joo] Ma'am.
- [woman 3] For your safety,
- please stand behind the yellow line.
- Are you okay? Come on. We gotta go.
- [Grandma moans, coughs]
- [grunts]
[sobbing] Oh, my Kyung-soo.
My dear, Kyung-soo.
- [indistinct announcement on PA]
- Stay close to the wall.
[woman 3] For your safety,
please stand behind...
It's dangerous. So, please just stay here.
[Grandma panting]
[woman 3] Please board
in an orderly fashion.
Please wait behind the yellow line.
[Young-joo gasps]
[Young-joo breathing shakily]
[exclaims] Hey, ma'am.
[train engine turns over]
[Young-joo grunting]
[screams]
[snarling]
[Young-joo] Ma'am. Ma'am.
- [Grandma snarls]
- [screaming]
[Grandma growling]
[screaming]
[Grandma continues growling]
[squelching]
[Young-joo crying]
[panting]
[pensive music playing]
[crying]
Yes,
[pensive music continues]
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
[softly] God, please help me.
[crashing]
[all whimpering]
[zombies snarling]
[both shouting]
[snarling]
[Paolo screaming]
[growls]
- [yelps]
- [both shouting]
[Paolo] Wait. I can handle this.
I can handle this.
- [zombie snarls]
- [all whimpering]
[zombies snarling]
Oh, oh! [panting]
[In-ho yelps, grunts]
- [Paolo] Move your foot.
- Just me, swear.
[Paolo] Just you, okay.
- [zombies snarling]
- Wait, wait.
Open up. Oh, shit. [yelps]
[zombie snarls]
- [all panting]
- [banging on door]
[In-ho chuckles]
- Fucking hell! Oh, God!
- [screaming]
Go! [panting] Look.
[Soo-jeong] Shit! We're stuck.
- Oh, shit. Access key.
- [banging on door]
Soo-jeong, look. It's a key.
- Then open the goddamn door.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, please. Please. Oh, shit.
- [door lock beeps]
- [zombies snarling]
- [Soo-jeong screams]
- [door lock chimes]
- [Gye-young] It worked. Get in.
- Get in.
- [Soo-jeong screams]
[zombie snarls]
- [both panting]
- [kisses]
[AC beeps]
[Soo-jeong] Huh?
[man 1 shouting]
[zombies snarling]
[man 2 panting]
Hey, hey, hey. Don't go that way.
Over there. The other side.
That way. That way.
Over there. Hurry up, and go now.
- [Young-man] Kyung-sik, hurry.
- Go!
[staple gun clicking]
Stupid piece of shit.
[growling]
[grunts]
- [grunting]
- [zombie snarls]
[Young-man] Manager. Hey, hurry up!
Huh? Shit.
- [both panting]
- Damn it!
- [Young-man] Come on. Go!
- Fucking hell.
- Damn it.
[Young-man] Come. This way.
Damn it.
Oh!
Kyung-sik! This one's open.
- Run, manager. Run, manager.
- [Kyung-sik] Go!
- [Young-man yelps] What're you doing?
- [Arron Park] No, don't close it.
Wait! Huh? What the hell?
- Hey, what's wrong with you?
- Letting him inside is suicide.
[banging on door]
[Arron Park] Come on. Open!
What's your problem?
[Young-man] Hey!
[Arron Park] Hey. Hey!
Have you lost it? Step aside.
I said move, damn it.
Get your fucking shit together, sir.
[Arron Park] Open the door! Hey!
[zombies snarling]
- [Arron Park sighs]
- [heroic music playing]
[zombies snarling]
[chuckles]
I suppose it's been a good run.
[grunts]
- [snarling]
- [heroic music continues]
- [music stops]
- [Arron Park] Hmm?
[comical music playing]
Want a bite? Maybe a nibble? Small one?
[comical music plays]
Why did you do that?
There was plenty of time to let him in.
With that bite on his ankle,
it's only a matter of time.
He'll eventually turn
into a zombie and murder us.
- This is serious.
- Hey!
- [doorbell chiming]
- Huh?
- [Kyung-sik] Huh?
- [doorbell chiming]
- [Arron Park] I'm not dead yet.
- [Kyung-sik] Huh?
And no bites either. Not one.
I have a feeling that
I'm not gonna die out here.
Forgive us, Manager Park.
No, no, no, no.
It's all right, Sergeant Kim.
There's no need to say sorry.
Private Hwang?
You got bitten. You've been infected.
- [zombie snarling]
- You're lying.
You're gonna attack us.
[Arron Park] Hey, Private.
I don't think I quite enjoy the way
that you're talking to me. [scoffs]
I mean...
Not that it matters. Let me tell you...
that I'll never forget this.
[zombie snarls]
[gasps]
[laughing]
Want a drink? Here we go.
Fuck that guy.
[door unlocks]
[hinges squeaking]
[machines whirring]
[woman] Young-joo.
- [emotional music playing]
- [Young-joo sobs]
[sniffles]
[zombies snarling]
[Young-joo sighs]
[woman] Young-joo.
[puzzling music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[woman] Young-joo.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
[breathing shakily]
[light clicks]
- [electricity whirring]
- [continues breathing shakily]
[cell phone vibrates]
MISSED CALLS
SWEET JAE-YOON
CALL FAILED
[sobbing]
[Paolo] Ah! We're completely surrounded.
Ah! Oh!
- Oh, Paolo! Oh.
- Huh?
- Paolo, where's your gun?
- Gun?
I... Elevator I think.
- [comical music playing]
- [In-ho exclaims]
- [radio beeps]
- [Paolo] Oh, what the fuck is happening?
- [radio static]
- What is all this?
Uh, is it the Three Calamities?
- Ah, this is insane.
- Private Lee Jae-yoon here.
Sergeant? Corporal?
Is everyone okay?
[on radio] This is
Corporal Kwak Gye-young.
Soo-jeong and I are okay.
[Young-man on radio] Uh, yeah.
Kyung-sik and I are also okay.
Ra In-Ho, Paolo and I are doing all right.
[radio static whooshing]
Any chance Arron Park is with you guys?
Uh, Arron Park isn't currently with us...
but he seems okay.
[both exhale deeply]
[Soo-jeong clears throat]
[both giggling awkwardly]
- That's funny.
- Oh, Soo-jeong.
I'll clean this up for you.
You can lie down and rest.
[Gye-young chuckles]
I don't want to.
Why the hell would I do that?
Huh? What is wrong with you, bro?
Okay, I see the issue. [chuckles]
Yeah. I think you're misunderstanding
what I'm trying to say here.
Maybe you'd like to relax?
That's not what I meant.
All I was trying to do was...
Usually, it's common courtesy to--
You know what?
Just forget it. Okay? Yeah. Yeah.
Just rest. Yeah, okay.
Huh.
[Young-joo strains]
[amusing music playing]
[groaning]
Employees pay for these?
[sighs] Public enterprise welfare, my ass.
[gasps]
[drum roll]
Awesome.
[whimpering] Oh, this really sucks.
[radio static, beeping]
[Young-man on radio]
We don't have enough ammo
to shoot our way through.
There's too many zombies.
[inhales, exhales]
There's gotta be
a safe way for us to get out.
Any ideas?
Do you guys think
we could blow up the zombies?
We could throw a few grenades
and then run downstairs.
That's impossible.
An explosion of that magnitude would
attract the attention of all the zombies.
[Jae-yoon sighs]
Cancel that.
[Soo-jeong sighs]
We have to conserve these,
if that's all that we've got.
- Hmm?
- All yours.
Oh, thank you.
KWAK GYE-YOUNG
INSTAGRAM: GYE_TO_THE_YOUNG
Hey, what is this?
Huh? Huh?
Oh.
[soft music playing]
f somehow we survive this,
I'd like to go on a date with you.
The thing is, you know,
I don't think it's really the time
for this kind of shit.
Yes. I know that,
but here's the thing, Soo-jeong.
[sighs] Uh, all of my entire life
I've always just sort of sat back
and gone with the flow.
Acting that way will get me killed now.
And I've realized
that I need a reason to live.
You make me want to live another day.
That's a brand new feeling for me.
What I'm trying to say is, you are...
the only motivation I need
to get through this.
Sure, I guess so.
You have to take me to a nice restaurant.
- You got it?
- [chuckles]
Well, it's a date, then.
[hesitates] Really? Okay.
Oh, Soo-jeong, seriously?
Oh. [hesitates]
Now the only option is survival.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, my God! [laughs]
Whatever.
[grunts]
What?
Okay.
[sighs] Does this thing even work?
DEFECTIVE
When it rains, it pours, doesn't it?
- [woman] Young-joo.
- [gasps]
Tch. Look at me putting my degree to work.
I guess mechanical engineering
is saving my life.
[woman] Young-joo.
Huh? What?
Will you give it a rest already? Ugh!
[sighs]
- [whirrs]
- [gasps]
- [whirring]
- [chuckles]
Hi-ya!
[chuckles]
MY NAME IS KANG YOUNG-JOO,
AND I'M BORROWING SOME EQUIPMENT
P.S. I HAD THE SOJU, NOODLES, AND CHIPS
[snarling]
[Jae-yoon sighs]
I don't think it's safe to go outside yet.
- [sighs] Huh?
- [Jae-yoon] What?
- [In-ho] I found it.
- Hey, Lee-Jae-yoon!
- What is it?
- I think we can use the vents to get out.
- [bell dings]
- Wait. [exclaims] Why's he outside? Wait.
- [chuckling]
Arron Park.
- Hold up, I'll get the door.
- [Arron] No, no.
[snarling]
- [Jae-yoon] Huh?
- The zombies don't bite me anymore.
Just don't put yourself in danger
by opening up the door.
They don't bite. But why?
Why? Great question.
There must be a reason why
Arron Park isn't changing.
Anyway...
You should know
that there's a way to get downstairs
without having to use
the hallways or elevators.
Wait, really? Where do we go?
See that vent in the middle of the room?
You can use it to escape.
The vent has a way out for all of you.
[chuckles] What do you think?
An excellent idea, right?
That is exactly what I was gonna say.
This is Private Lee Jae-yoon.
Sergeant Kim Young-man.
Corporal Kwak Gye-young, can you read me?
Corporal Kwak Gye-young, awaiting orders.
I'm here too.
[Jae-yoon] Everyone, pay attention.
I'll go over the escape plan
that Arron Park and I put together.
All of your rooms should have a vent
right in the center of the ceiling.
You'll first need to open the ventilator.
You'll then need to widen
the ventilation entrance to fit through.
[thudding]
[Jae-yoon] Use your rifles
or anything strong enough
to start breaking down the wall.
Although the vents should be empty,
we've seen hordes of zombies
every single step of the way.
So make sure to always be on the look.
Once inside the ventilation system,
you'll have to navigate it
and reach the main vent.
From there, we'll have a direct way out
via the access ladders.
Given the situation in the hallway,
I think this is our best option.
Okay, so we'll enter the vent
in exactly 30 minutes.
[Gye-young] Okay.
Working on widening the entrance.
[thudding]
[Arron] Whoa, whoa, there. [sighs]
[snarling]
Uh... Excuse me.
Oh, oh, oh.
Mrs. Kim shame on you.
How many times did I ask you
not to drink at work, huh?
[sighs]
Three stashed bottles. Jeez, lady.
[clears throat]
[gulping]
Ah!
[Gye-young] We just have
to follow the vents, right?
How will we know which way to go?
[Jae-yoon] Arron Park
will be guiding us through the vents.
He supervised
the ventilation system's construction
and knows the layout by heart.
He'll mark arrows to show the right path
we must take to reach the main vent.
All our team needs to do
is follow the arrows.
That's the plan.
We must be quick and quiet.
Sergeant Kim Young-man,
Corporal Kwak Gye-young,
awaiting your orders.
Yes. We're all set here.
Corporal Kwak Gye-young.
We're ready to go.
Good luck to everyone.
See you all on the other side!
How was that?
Yeah. Gye-young is right, you guys.
Everyone, make it out alive.
That's an order.
Directly from your squad commander.
- Yes, sir!
- Sir, yes, sir.
- Dumb asses.
- All squad members,
are now clear to begin their escape route.
[In-ho grunting]
Paolo, take my hand. Grab it.
[Soo-jeong] Be careful.
[grunting] Are you worried about me?
[Soo-jeong] Shut up and climb!
[grunting]
Hey, you see the arrows?
Fucking hell.
Kyung-sik! Wait for me.
Ah, shit. [pants]
[coughing]
[Jae-yoon] Turn left. Turn left.
[panting]
Let's do this.
[whirring]
Okay.
[snarling]
[whirring]
[screaming]
Shit!
[snarling]
[screams]
[panting]
Hold on.
All the arrows are gone.
[Arron] What's up?
[laughs] You actually made it.
Are you okay, Paolo?
No.
I'm fine, Arron.
Let's just keep going, okay?
God, I'm so hot.
Hey, so, how far away are we?
Almost there.
We're five minutes away,
so come on, let's go.
Okay, let's go.
[grunting, panting]
[Jae-yoon] Go, go, go. Go, go.
Where the fuck are the arrows?
[strains]
Hey, wait. Soo-jeong. Soo-jeong.
- Huh?
- You're, um...
You're tensing up your body.
You'll get tired quicker
and won't advance much.
What you need to do is relax your body
and use both your forearms
to push and you gradually move forward.
[grunts] Like this.
Oh.
Like this? Oh!
It's way easier like this.
Right?
Like this. Like this.
Like this.
I don't really have many talents,
but I did win first place in boot camp
for crawling.
[Soo-jeong] Jesus Christ. [chuckles]
[Gye-young] Not like that.
Relax your lower body.
- Like this?
- [Gye-young] Like this.
[Soo-jeong] What are you doing?
Check out the backwards crawl.
This one's on your back. Like this.
- Huh?
- [snarling]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[snarling]
[Soo-jeong] Gye-young, get it together.
We still have to go on a date! [sighs]
- Come on! Come on!
- Over there! That way!
[screams]
[grunting]
[snarling]
Soo-jeong, just a bit more.
Just keep going.
[grunting]
[screaming]
[snarling]
Oh, my God!
[screams]
[music playing]